

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

**Programming Languages** 

C#

PYTHON

SQL (ORACLE SOL)

SQL (SQL SERVER)

**Languages** 

ENGLISH

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Motivated
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player

### CONTACT

Fast learner

E: cemilbyhn1571@gmail.com P:+905078329766

#### SOCIAL

linkedin.com/in/mehmetcemilbayhan/github.com/cemilbayhan medium.com/@cemilbyhn1571/kaqqle.com/cemlbayhan

# MEHMET CEMIL BAYHAN

COMPUTER ENGINEERING STUDENT

## **ABOUT**

I'm still studying at department of Computer Science Marmara University. I've also worked as IT support technician at Marmara University. My interests are Database Development, Business Intelligence and Java Development. I always try to develop myself with all my strength. Nowadays, I established a club(foundation) named "Marmara SoftPath" in which all students can join according to their interests and do project about software.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

The whole details about my all work experiences are been in my LinkedIn profile.

### IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Marmara University | Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

### **BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE INTERN**

Bibilen Training and Consultancy | 2 Aug - 28 Sept 2021

#### VICE PRESIDENT

Marmara SoftPath Student Community | November 2021 - Present

### **EDUCATION**

## COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Marmara University | 2019 - 2023

## AWARDS

Not yet